what?
何?
何ですか?
Excuse me, what is it?
すみません、何ですか?
What do you mean?
何ですかって言うのは?
Yes, huh?
はい、え?
What, what happened?
え、どうしたの?
Did something happen?
何かあった?
There's nothing.
何もないよ
Did anything interesting happen?
面白いことあった?
I thought it was kind of cute.
ちょっと可愛いなと思って
Can I take a picture?
撮っちゃっていいですか?
Because it's good.
うまいから
It's so good, can I take a picture of it?
うまいから撮っていい?
Just as a souvenir.
ちょっと、記念に
yes.
はい
I think it will happen twice later.
後で2回そうかなって
But it makes me laugh so much.
でもめっちゃ笑うじゃん
Because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Can we have a Q&A session for a little while?
ちょっとね、いろいろね、 質問コーナーをしていいですか?
ah.
あー
How old are you now?
今は、5年齢は?
I'm 20 years old.
20歳です
Ah, it's red.
あ、赤いっすね
It's red.
赤いんです
Are you doing any work now?
今は何か仕事とかしてるの?
I'm currently working at my current office.
今は、 現務の事務所の方に入って
Masu.
ます
That's amazing.
すごい ね
Surprisingly.
意外と
Surprisingly?
意外と?
Not surprising at all.
全然意外じゃないけど
I thought it was like that.
そのままだと思ったよ
It's cute.
可愛いしね
I took a quick look at it a while ago.
ちょっとチラッとさっき、 覗きましたけど
Are you working hard?
頑張ってる?
I'm doing it.
してる
Are you doing any exercise?
運動とかしてるの?
Oh, do you have abs?
あ、腹筋してるの?
every day?
毎日?
every day.
毎日
It may be surprising.
意外かもしれない
But isn't it amazing?
でもすごいじゃない?
That's right.
そうだよ
It's a job that people can see.
人に見られる 仕事だもんね
What is that?
それは何?
Have you been doing this for a long time?
ずっとやってるの?
Not forever.
ずっとじゃないです
From this year?
こ っちと、 今年から?
I started properly.
ちゃんと始めたの
Until then, just a little.
それまでは、 ちょっとね
Other job?
他の仕事?
If you're a baseball fan, I think you might like it.
野球好きな人だったらね、 好きじゃないかなって 思うんです
Right.
よね
Is that so?
そう なの?
Hey.
へー
Sounds like it, that's for sure.
いそうだね、確かに
Is that Tokyo?
それは東京?
I was given the opportunity to do it in Tokyo.
東京でやらせて いただいてました
Tokyo Dome?
東京ドーム?
that's right.
そうです
I heard that it's quite difficult.
なかなかなるの厳しいって 聞きましたけど
It's becoming more popular.
人気が上がってますからね
amazing.
すごい
It's really just a household budget.
ほんま家計だね
I see.
そっか
That's fine too, so let's go to Herzer.
あれも結構だから、ハーザーにね、
It's quite a physical job, isn't it?
なかなか体力仕事でしょ?
It's heavy.
重いですからね
Yeah, it's tough.
ね、大変だよね
Huh, what is that and where are you from?
え、 それは何か、出身はどっかな?
different.
違う
Oh, you came to Tokyo?
あ、上京してきたの?
Where is it?
どこなんですか?
Hey.
へー
Oh, what about there?
あ、そこは?
Want to hide it?
隠したい?
It's fine.
別にいいですよ
Do you want to hide it?
それは 隠したい?
Fukuoka.
福岡
What?
え、何?
This is Fukuoka.
福岡です
Oh, it's Fukuoka.
あ、福岡なんだ
He taught me.
教えてくれた
That's okay, personal information, that's it.
いいよ別に、個人情報、それが
No, that's not the case now.
いやいや、今はそうじゃないね
I understand.
よく分かる
Fukuoka is full of beautiful parks.
福岡はやっぱね、 きれいな公園もね
In Fukuoka?
福岡の?
No, no.
いやいや
Number 1.
1番の
Is it true?
本当ですか?
It's cute though.
かわいいんだけど
To.
へ ー
Do you have a boyfriend now?
彼氏は今いる?
I'm here.
います
Ah, there it is.
あ、いるんだ
Is it quite long?
結構長いですか?
It's insanely long.
めちゃくちゃ長い
What is high school?
高校ってことは何?
Is your boyfriend over there now?
今彼氏はあっちにいる?
I agree.
そうですね
I went to higher education there, so I feel like I'm the only one here.
向こうで進学しちゃったんで、 私だけこっちに出てきた感じ
long distance love.
遠距離恋愛
that's right.
そうです
Can I see you?
会えてますか?
I haven't seen you at all.
全然会えてない
Not at all.
全然じゃん
That's sad.
悲しいですね
picture?
え?
How can I contact you?
連絡は?
I've been in touch.
連絡はしてますよ
Not so much lately.
最近はあんまり
I made phone calls every day.
毎日毎日、うち通話とかやったけど
Hey, I haven't seen you at all.
へー、全然会えてないんだね
I miss you.
寂しいです
lonely?
寂しい?
Just a little bit of loneliness.
ちょっとじゃあ、寂しさを
Loneliness.
寂しさを
Can I heal you?
癒しちゃおうかな?
please.
ぜひ
Oh, by all means?
あ、ぜひ?
Can it be healed?
癒せるかな?
I wonder if I can heal it.
癒せるかなって
Can I heal you?
俺が癒してもらえるの?
It's cute.
可愛いね
I think I'll take a look at some things.
ちょっと色々見ちゃおうかな
yeah?
ん?
Let's take a look.
見 ちゃおう
I was a little embarrassed, so I thought I'd give it a try.
ちょっと恥ずかしいから、 しようかなって思った
I think it's good.
いいと思います
When was the last time you met your boyfriend?
最後に彼氏と会ったのはいつなの?
8 months ago.
8ヶ月前
Oh, not at all.
え、全然じゃん
Did you have a hot night then?
その時は、 暑い夜を過ごしたんですか?
Be kind.
優しめで
Kind?
優しめの?
Will you do it?
や る?
When was the last time you did something naughty like that?
最後に そういう エッチいことしたのって いつなの?
The last time was about 2 months ago.
最後にしたのは 2ヶ月前ぐらい
Isn't he a handsome actor?
イケメン俳優でしょ?
Is it different?
違う の?
違うの?
Isn't it Johnny's Talent or something?
ジャニーズタレントとかじゃないの?
What should I do?
なんでしよう
Eh, who?
え、誰?
A little bit, a bit of a big thing, a big thing?
ちょっとある ちょっと大物の 大物の?
A big man?
お偉いさん?
But that's right.
なんです けど そうですね
What did the great man do?
偉い人って何したの?
What is the situation?
どういう状況?
I want to know.
私が知りたい
I want to know?
私が知りたい?
Is that the dark side of the industry?
そういう 業界の闇的な?
Is there such a thing?
そういうのあるんだ?
Is it for work?
仕事のため的なこと?
I just got it after all, so I'll have to work a little harder to sell it.
やっぱり入ったばっかりなんで 売り出すにはもうちょっと 頑張
They made me work hard because I knew I couldn't do anything without them.
ら ないとダメだよって 頑張らさせられました
I learned so many things from that great man.
い ろんなことを教わったのじゃ その お偉いさんね
Do you do it yourself?
自 分でさ したりするの?
Oh, are you going to do it?
あ、するの?
What kind of fan do you want?
どういう ファンにするの?
Will you?
するの?
What do you mean?
どういう?
Hey, how many times do you try it and how do you do it?
ちょっと 何回やってみて どうやってやるの?
Where do you touch it?
どこ触るの?
Don't you understand?
分かんないか?
That's Cree, huh?
そういうの クリー え?
picture?
え?
What did you say?
なんて言った?
Cree Cretalis I don't know where.
クリー クリータリス ちょっとそれ 分かんないんだけど どこ
Is there something in it?
に あるものなの?
Give it a try, I don't understand.
それは ちょっとやってみてよ 分かんないんだよ
Around here, is that a knee?
この 辺 それは膝 膝?
It's not around here, right?
この辺じゃないでしょ?
Where is it?
どこにあるもの?
Just point your finger at me
ちょっと指で差し示してみて
What should we do about that?
そ こをどうする?
Wet your fingers to study
勉強のために 指を濡らして
Naderu eh?
な でる え?
Wet your fingers and kiss them. Stroke them. Try it. Try it.
指を濡らして くいくいする なでてあげる やってみて やって
Look, try, try What does "try" mean?
み て やってみて やってみてって何?
Stroke me a little?
ちょっと なでる?
How strong is it?
どのくらい強いの?
Try it and make it stronger
やって みて 強め か
I like it, it's really cute
わ いいね めちゃくちゃ めちゃくちゃかわいいね
It's definitely naughty
絶 対やらしいじゃん
I don't think so. That's right.
じゃない と思ってます そうなんだ
Can you confirm?
確 かめる?
She has a very erotic face
すごいエロい顔になってる
Can you touch it?
触 るか
Can you feel it being touched?
触 られる 感じちゃうの?
Amazing legs
すごい足きれい
She's so beautiful. She's definitely a model. Take care.
め ちゃくちゃきれいじゃん さすがモデルさんだね 気をつか
That's great. Food?
ってる ね えらいね 食事とか?
Yeah, I'm starting to be more careful lately.
うん 最近気をつかうようになります あ、
That's right, for work.
そうなんだ 仕事のために
That's right. If you are careful when eating, there may be a slight smell.
あれ だね 食事とかは気をつかってると ちょっと匂いとかも
If you don't check it out, it might smell a little because she's a model.
確 認しておかないと ちょっと匂いちゃうか モデルさんだから
Oh, anyone can smell feet.
あ 足だ匂いするって誰でも 両方
It smells a little like sweat, but it also smells like roses.Why?
ちょ っぴり汗の匂いが でもなんかバラ匂いがするよ なんで?
I wonder why
なんでだろう
With such naughty feet
こんな やらしい足でさ
I gave this to the producer who did this for me.
こう いうのやってあげたのプロデューサーさんに やってあげた
Oh, I was made to do it.
の あ、やらされたんだ
Chin Chin what's going on?
チ ンチンどうなってる
There are also pants
パ ンツもある
What, aren't these pants weak?
何 このパンツ 弱くない?
Not weak, huh?
弱くない え?
What is this?
何これ?
Come closer, aren't you hooked?
近づいて スケじゃない?
This is so cool
これ スケてるよね
Yeah, is this included?
うん こんなの入ってるの?
Is it open?
開かされてるの?
No, it's included
違う 入ってます
Because it's cute, it's already cute, but it's cute.
可愛 いから もう可愛いんだけど 可愛いんだけどさ
When I first met you, you were amazing. I thought you were some sort of cleaning person, but...
最 初 会った時すごいさ なんか清掃系なのかと思ったけど ド
It will scale, right?
ス ケるでしょ ん?
Dosuke Rude
ドスケるで
I'm going to do something naughty.
しょ えっちなことするから
You came here because you wanted to do something naughty.
え っちなこと したくて来てくれたんだよね
Because I felt sorry for you. Because I felt sorry for you?
か わいそうだったから かわいそうだったから?
You've been messing with me all this time, haven't you? What?
ずっといじってくれてるじゃん 何?
Why do you feel sorry for me?
何でかわいそう?
What do you mean by standing up?
立ってるから なんて?
Do you like cock because it looks tight?
きつそうだから チン好きなの?
Do you like dick?
チ ン好き?
You're touching me so much
すげえ触ってるじゃん
I'm sleeping. Why are you sleeping?
寝 てる なんで寝ちゃったんだ?
I don't understand, you like dick, right?
わからない チンチン好きでしょ
like?
好 き?
Which do you prefer, beer or Chin Chin?
ビールとチンチンどっちが好き?
Not at all. I was a little worried. Do you like both?
全然 ちょっと悩んだね どっちも好きなの?
Great, great, they're sitting down. Don't look yet. Sit down directly.
すごい すごい座ってくるじゃん まだ見ちゃダメだよ 直接座り
That's right.
た そうだね
cute
か わいい
You wore such cute clothes.
す げえかわいい服で 着てくれたんだね
favorite
お 気に入りの
I was surprised because I was dressed like this. My underwear was tight.
こんな 格好だからびっくりしちゃった 下着が あみくっていれ
Is it okay?
ば いい?
Ah, should I stay with you?
あ、あみくっていればいいの?
I want to see it.
見たい
Then turn around.
じゃあ後ろ向いてさ
Show me the back too.
後ろも見せてよ
It's a tea bag.
ティーバッグなんだよ
ティーバッグなんだ
That's naughty.
やらしい
Look at this too.
こっちも見て
You're sensitive.
敏感だね
Just leave it there, put your hand down.
そのままさ、なんか下にさ、手ついちゃってよ
can?
できる?
Like posing Nana.
ナナをポーズみたいな
He has really good legs.
めちゃくちゃいい足してる
Have you ever dressed like this?
こんな格好したことある?
Isn't it because she's a model?
モデルさんやってるからあるんじゃない?
It's so squishy.
すごいくちゅうくちゅうだよ
That's naughty.
やらしい
I want to watch it forever.
ずっと見てたい
Okay, then take a look here too.
いい よ、じゃあこっちも見てごらん
Well, now that's it, why don't you take it off?
じゃあさ、もうそれさ、脱いちゃえば?
Yeah.
うん
Let's take it off.
脱いちゃおうよ
Isn't it hot?
熱いでしょ?
It's hot.
熱いで
It's so hot.
めっちゃ熱い
amazing.
すごい
what up
どうした
of?
の?
Why is it so big?
なん でかくすの?
I'm angry.
腹かいてる
Wow, that's amazing.
うわ、すごいじゃん
What what what?
なになになに?
What?
な になに?
That's amazing, I'm sure you have abs.
すごいね、確かに、腹筋が
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃかわいいね
what?
なに?
It's so tight,
ぎゅーってさ、
cute.
か わいい
So cute.
すげーかわいい
It's so naughty.
すっごいやらしい
delicious?
おいしい?
delicious.
おいしい
A little bit with your voice.
声でちょっと
You're sensitive.
敏感だね
Look, it's moving on its own.
ほら、自分で動いちゃってるじゃん
You want to take it off quickly, right?
早く脱いたいんでしょ
Those are beautiful breasts.
綺麗なおっぱいだね
Messed up.
めちゃくちゃ
delicious.
おいしい
It's really delicious.
めっちゃおいしいよ
Amazing, amazing.
すっごい、すっごい
You're sensitive.
敏感だね
Show me both sides.
両脇見せて
check.
チェック
Will it be checked?
チェックされるでしょ?
Very
めちゃ
It seems to be a mess.
く ちゃやらしい
I want to see it from behind, so I'm on the verge of it.
後ろから見たいから、寸前になって
Kneel there.
そこ、ひざつけて
Ah, here, yes.
あ、ここ、そう
That's right, that's right.
そうだ、そうだ
He looked amazing.
すごいっちな格好だったよね
It's already sticking out.
もうはみ出てるね
Oh, that's amazing.
おー、すごい
I'm just looking at your butthole.
お尻の穴だけ見てるよ
You're sleeping soundly.
ぺっとり寝てるね
He's looking really naughty right now.
めちゃくちゃ今、やらしい格好してるよ
rice cake?
もち?
Wow, I'm twitching.
すごい、ひくひくしてる
From the left, turn this way.
左からさ、こっち向いて
I'll point you out.
指出ちゃうよ
tight.
きつい
It's really tight.
すごい きつい
It's very narrow.
すごい狭い
It's slimy.
ぬるぬるだね
It's really tough.
すーごいきつい
This is amazing.
すごいよ、これ
With my feet on it.
足 のっけで
Why do you hide it?
なんで隠すの?
Show me your boobs properly.
ちゃんとおっぱいを見せて
No.
ダメだよ
Is it different?
違うの?
By yourself, with both hands, open your pussy and show me.
自分でさ、両手でさ、 おまんご開いて見せて
Hey, hey.
ちょ、おい
That's what I'll show you myself.
そんな自分で見せてくれるんだ
It's beautiful.
きれいだね
It's so beautiful.
め ちゃくちゃきれい
Don't you know?
わかんないか?
I've never seen it before.
見たことないもんね
I'm talking really twitchy.
すごいひくひく言ってるよ
why?
なんで?
I guess it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいかな
Do you like it here?
ここが好きなの?
I'm excited.
くりくりしてる
I'm sleeping a lot.
すっごい寝てるよ
what happened?
どうしたの?
It closes really well.
すっごい閉まる
It's so messy.
すっごいべちゃべちゃだね
Awesome.
すっごい
Soaked.
びしょびしょ
It's soaking wet.
びしょびしょになっちゃったね
Ku-cha-kucha-so-gebecha.
く ちゃくちゃすっげーべちゃ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?